

### ♣ Profile

Well-qualified mobile developer with advanced skills on Flutter and Android. Studying Clean Architecture, SOLID, TDD, Design Patterns and Refactoring. I'm committed to the best way to produce high-quality softwares, following good principles and techniques of the Software Engineering. I have more than 3 years of related experience with software development.

# ★ Favorite technologies



# Employment history

Mobile developer at Megaleios

June 2021 - Present

Mobile developer at Bean Softwares

March 2021 - June 2021

Mobile developer at Thalamus Digital

July 2020 - June 2021

Mobile developer at MFIT Personal

January 2020 - May 2020

## Education

Computer Science at Univali

February 2020 - Present

**English at KNN Idiomas** 

September 2020 - Present

# Projects

## Entrepreneur at iCut

May 2021 - Present

A barber appointment app. Available on icut.app

## Voluntary coding instructor

May 2021 - Present

Teaching some friends how to code.

#### **Entrepreneur at StudentPlus**

August 2018 - April 2021

A study planner. Available on Google Play

### **Details**

Itajaí, SC, Brazil

contact@lucasbatista.me

## Links

LinkedIn

GitHub

WhatsApp

Website

### Skills

**UI/UX** Design

TDD

**DevOps** 

**UML** 

**Design Patterns** 

**SOLID** 

Clean Architecture

# Languages

**English** 

### **Hobbies**

Hackathons, pair programming, teaching, code kata and reading.